rentalcargroup.com 2016-08-21

# 🚗 Privacy Policy - RentalCarGroup car hire, car rental with all-inclusive rates

## We offer a price comparison of all major and independent car rental suppliers

**We  know how serious you are about your personal privacy. We value our customer relationship with you and we keep your privacy in mind. You have a right to know how we use the personal data we collect in order to help you with your car hire.**

The following represents our privacy policy regarding the collection, handling, and distribution of your personal data.  
The information we collect is used:

  * to conduct a business transaction with you 
  * to ensure compliance with legal processes 
  * to improve the content on our website 
  * to notify company partners of your reservation request

**Information collection**  
The personal information we collect may contain all of the information you have provided to us to make a reservation and rent you a car. This includes your name, address, telephone number, email address, employer, date of birth, driver's license number, credit card information and your rental history. We gather this information from our site or via our call centers.  
We share this information with the car rental franchisees that provide you a rental car. When necessary, we may also pass this information to third parties to enforce collection efforts against you as a result of the breach of any agreement with us.

**Security**  
We protect our customer information. Any personal data we receive through our site is protected and encrypted by Secure Socket Layer (SSL). We have taken what we believe to be reasonable steps to ensure your personal data is accessible only to those whom we designate.

###### Opening Hours

[EST] Mon - Fri: 03:00 - 16:00  Sat - Sun : 03:00 - 11:00

[GMT] Mon - Fri: 08:00 - 23:00  Sat - Sun : 08:00 - 16:00

###### Contact us by Phone

  * United States (++1) 866 735 1715 Germany 0800 789 5047
  * United Kingdom (++44) 0800 078 9054 Spain (++34) 914 141 480
  * Australia (++61) 1800 210 813 France (++33) 170 700 593
  * Netherlands (++31) 0800 020 0459 Belgium (++32) 02 400 4165
